Guide to the Trude B. Feldman papers, Circa 1941 - Circa 2013 MS2343
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Adolph Eichmann trial, circa 1960-1965; Series 8
  - Newspaper clippings, 1960-1962; Series 8 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1961; Series 8 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1960-1961; Series 8 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1960-1962; Series 8 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1960; Series 8 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1960-1962; Series 8 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Case files 2 & 50, 1961; Series 8 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - German court documents 605-1239, Undated; Series 8 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Reporters notes & drafts, 1960; Series 8 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Genose Münchhausen (Story), 1962; Series 8 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Request for Legal Assistance (in German), 1961; Series 8 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Case files 1-6 (Appeal), 1962; Series 8 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Appeal Court documents, 1962; Series 8 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Case files Judgement, 1962; Series 8 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Case files Judgement, 1962; Series 8 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Case files 5-20, 1961; Series 8 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Case files 30-58, 1961; Series 8 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Case files 70-79, 1961; Series 8 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Case files 70-74, 1961; Series 8 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Case files 80-89, 1961; Series 8 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Case files 93-100, 1961; Series 8 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Case files 107-114, 1961; Series 8 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Case files 90-120, 1961; Series 8 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Attorney General's opening remarks, undated; Series 8 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Adolf Eichmann Police D'Israel, Undated; Series 8 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Case files miscellaneous, 1961; Series 8 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Audio related to Adolf Eichmann Trial, 1960-1962; Series 8 (Box 33)
  - Audio related to Adolf Eichmann Trial, 1960-1962; Series 8 (Box 34)
  - Audio related to Adolf Eichmann Trial, 1960-1962; Series 8 (Box 35)
  - Audio related to Adolf Eichmann Trial, 1960-1962; Series 8 (Box 36)